## ANTONIO RUFINO CASASUS - Full Stack Developer



## Profile

Full-Stack programmer with 1+ years of experience developing and maintaining web applications.

I've designed and developed advanced applications from use cases and functional requirements. I'm always trying to expand my knowledge so I'm not afraid at all to face new technologies.



## **Experience**

## Assembler Institute of Technology

October 2022 - Now

#### Full Stack Developer

- · Web project based on an e-commerce with the React.js library, authentication with Google, and payment gateway with Stripe, with a backend developed with the Java framework, Spring Boot and using MySQL as database.
- Programming in Node.js for the creation of a streaming audio platform, designed with React.js and Redis, using MongoDB as database.
- · Projects developed in teams of 2-4 members, among which I have always acted as Scrum Master at the request of the group.

## Artifact Consulting SLU

May 2022 - October 2022

## Java Backend Developer

- · Java programming with Spring Tool Suite with Spring Boot framework (Spring MVC, Spring Data, Spring REST) using JPA, Thymeleaf for CRUD web applications and also integration of web systems with embedded systems (IoT with UDP).
- Java programming and technical debt refactoring with Eclipse IDE working with JSP, Servlet, Javascript, HTML and CSS in legacy web projects.
- · Use of complex SQL's on MySQL Workbench to develop custom queries in Spring Data using JPQL.
- Tortoise SVN for version control, WinMerge for merge resolution.

#### Sistemas2 Valencia - Audiovisual Technician

June 2017 - February 2022



## Education

#### Máster in Software Development (1.200 hours)

October 2022 - June 2023 | Assembler Institute of Technology

#### Front-End Development (300 hours)

March 2022 - Now | Tokio School

## Programming in Java OCP (300 hours)

September 2021 - June 2022 | Tokio School

## Higher Level Training Cycle - Telecommunications y Computer Systems (2.000 hours)

September 2015 – June 2017 | Vicente Blasco Ibañez

#### CCNA1 Routing & Switching (180 hours)

September 2016 - June 2017 | Cisco Networking Academy



## Contact

St Muro 3, 412, 03560 El Campello, Alicante





https://www.linkedin.com/in/devs-toni/



https://arcprojects.es



#### **Programming Languages**

Java - PHP - Typescript - Javascript

#### Java

Servlet - JSP - Tomcat - Maven - Java FX Spring Boot - Spring Data - Spring MVC - Spring Rest Spring Security - Spring Session - Thymeleaf

#### Web Development

Next - React - Node - HTML - CSS - Tailwind **Bootstrap** 

#### **Database**

MySQL - MongoDB - Elastic Search - Redis

#### Deploy

Linux - Docker - Apache2

#### Version control - Scrum

Git [Github] - Tortoise SVN - WinMerge Jira - JMS - Click Up - Github Projects

#### **Others**

Apache Kafka - Stripe - OAuth - Android Studio Google Speech - HTTP Rest

## 🛍 Languages

English - B2

Spanish - Native

Valencian - Native

# Personal Projects

On my website you can find everything related to my professional profile as well as all the projects I have been doing to improve my technical skills, some of them in collaboration helping me also to improve my social skills.



## **Team Work**

- Adaptation
- Communication
- Resilience
- Organisation
- Initiative
- Responsability
- Critical Thinking